<xml xmlns="https://developers.google.com/blockly/xml" is_dbot="true" collection="false">
  <variables>
    <variable id="aD0I2PPK3p_}A@z(vb0P">STAKE</variable>
    <variable id="=RZ25D}(}1+x^lQYjm6x">INITIAL STAKE</variable>
    <variable id="fCxrNtvK86,pspiRZF?H">STOP LOSS</variable>
    <variable id="+f8F|SI?-?BK*EMV0tF?">entry point</variable>
    <variable id="NDjP(.1O#Q;|,|Ri0qmI">TAKE PROFIT</variable>
    <variable id="SJ-8/}6],4aC/?FT3w#R">digit 1</variable>
    <variable id="F9Hixb-C#0?IY2W5a`)g">MARTIGALE</variable>
    <variable id="qQ4L;=/HEy_{v-$mIlib">digit 2</variable>
    <variable id="x5D^m:A*o?rK3Y_hIe*S">last digit txt</variable>
  </variables>
  <block type="trade_definition" id="kWc71{X;skxFcqgN1^0U" deletable="false" x="0" y="110">
    <statement name="TRADE_OPTIONS">
      <block type="trade_definition_market" id=".[[NF!N}rQHI?TMdyZT:" deletable="false" movable="false">
        <field name="MARKET_LIST">synthetic_index</field>
        <field name="SUBMARKET_LIST">random_index</field>
        <field name="SYMBOL_LIST">1HZ50V</field>
        <next>
          <block type="trade_definition_tradetype" id="8_=p]#QZDPxztQufh.de" deletable="false" movable="false">
            <field name="TRADETYPECAT_LIST">digits</field>
            <field name="TRADETYPE_LIST">evenodd</field>
            <next>
              <block type="trade_definition_contracttype" id="zXHw5#q_AU;@f;A$q819" deletable="false" movable="false">
                <field name="TYPE_LIST">DIGITODD</field>
                <next>
                  <block type="trade_definition_candleinterval" id="Mr/7d@t2KzL!}Aa#PcJj" deletable="false" movable="false">
                    <field name="CANDLEINTERVAL_LIST">60</field>
                    <next>
                      <block type="trade_definition_restartbuysell" id="CGZOq-=_tsZ`EtTTlm)4" deletable="false" movable="false">
                        <field name="TIME_MACHINE_ENABLED">FALSE</field>
                        <next>
                          <block type="trade_definition_restartonerror" id="b$bq?茶鳌钼ㄨ佯嗥溴戾翎忪褰㈡犰箦盹鲠忪褰㈡犰箦⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰遗釉烈韵闻乙弦⒕砸张集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰晌稍闪躺诹陨衔⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮箦簪殇舰葶涠柝醛编愿椟肮饕症兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰崮吧残兴仇啐晾鲡靶⒕釉了偶骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰诚封拄许贩Ｖか擅酯⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷敬狗集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮箦簪殇舰╅链庹匕藻璺赫掀觯⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰揭诓的鲍揿奄觏而⒕晌稍闪釉了偶骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰纥禚韧爷遨叶赎缯ㄣ骤⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷敬狗集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮箦簪殇舰屮镪ハ矿嬷融咭ㄊ⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰婷蛭赧烁冬痼痖亿瓶娶居韵滔佑集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰钤吲碜婪疹玻痛炖盯兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷镜凹骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮箦簪殇舰疔扃疰醚∞蚯宜祯衅＂兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰文晷ó毕Ｑ稽议榜砩⒕粤伺幸掀稍集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰铧戽嗡熘灬房酿硅掩⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷颈蛋集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮箦簪殇舰拯名紧蛳饶哑坪二光邰兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰乒乳猸茫翱少沧滇喋纰就烈陨橇膛集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰琢棋樽弼恳狯腌陷并兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷静集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰诱峦烈伺寓尖祜汶豉疱舰泔铘蝻祗唛姊殇舰艳郯结╆谝憩陇称堪匦泔祆狃箦浣Ⅳ蝓澧柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱屐箦舰雹炯眭翎糸镱荐犰蹂钺礤舰善阿尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮蜻痱镳弪豉殇舰土罚厅答后模肃╃坝せ⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱溟鲩箫蜻轭瘐艚㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰幸闲乓再⒕胖盼集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰握吐乓咴线萌琶刷俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰摺独杳阁筠滏津如猕并兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景集骈屐渚集箬徜秣尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰该乇烧襻磁垛铱闱澄⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰娓泣由凯柯霜磐职羝竣惧铘蝙痫轭艏骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南阿尖祜汶豉疱舰泔铘蝻祗唑屦遽暨屮簪殇舰善焓松逵贯纱篡忆薜铫荐犰蹂钺礤舰陨团英尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳咩镱篝犷簪殇舰瑛琨牟钲祢奁唼篝あ兼殄熹钺礤舰孟斡粤卧⒕晌粕紊再集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰糸礤秕簪殇舰另阐活夫访黑企瘦旰躺⒕俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰陨团险杂粤盟⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰铒糸纟殇舰锢迢履孔芥忮梓醢酰⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰蜗陨粕昧陨衔咴傩泞倔蹉沐篌集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰蜗陨粕昧陨衔哂险文⒕箝戾铘集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰团佑燎泞俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰刺撺椤配娴榨翱镟嵊⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕徕慵骈屐渚集箬徜秣尖祜汶豉疱舰灬篝咪殓轸殇舰纵盔牾苛枉る枚坞⒕集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰泔铘蝻祗唛姊殇舰鳝藉谚衾父眩灌鳇痢虎荐犰蹂钺礤舰善阿尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮蜻痱镳弪豉殇舰挂翎焯丧滕鸫揩讵袍罐⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱溟鲩箫蜻轭瘐艚㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰幸闲乓再⒕胖盼集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰握吐乓咴线萌琶刷俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰摺独杳阁筠滏津如猕并兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景集骈屐渚集箬徜秣尖祜汶豉疱舰灬篝咪殓轸殇舰芭褪豆耧懦耠∥冒罚丌炯忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南阿尖祜汶豉疱舰泔铘蝻祗哝祜鬟篝狒屙孱趔殇舰肥闷稀腹健阱欣黢属⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰铺献⒕乱帕思骈屐渚集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟荐犰蹂钺礤舰优孟文英尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰埕▲湮域诱洙膘赚园⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰盘优⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰泔铘蝻祗唑屦遽暨屮簪殇舰瓮惨团穷迸蛆慎市扔洧荐犰蹂钺礤舰陨团英尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳咩镱篝犷簪殇舰鹫辗蓓憬把篾黹颃琚兼殄熹钺礤舰孟斡粤卧⒕晌粕紊再集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰糸礤秕簪殇舰业怃逞聃平探隰钳蘑俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰陨团险杂粤盟⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰铒糸纟殇舰锊轵常眩硎莸悌哔砼蘑兼殄熹钺礤舰蜗陨粕昧陨衔咴傩泞倔蹉沐篌集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰蜗陨粕昧陨衔哂险文⒕箝戾铘集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰团佑燎泞俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰刺撺椤配娴榨翱镟嵊⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕徕慵骈屐渚集箬徜秣尖祜汶豉疱舰灬篝咪殓轸殇舰瞳鹜夫历矢霍临尿抓⒕集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰泔铘蝻祗唛姊殇舰孔惚仄截〈醛诏乌涪荐犰蹂钺礤舰善阿尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮蜻痱镳弪豉殇舰诧栋ヌ载陔綮叫彪摆澧柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱溟鲩箫蜻轭瘐艚㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰幸闲乓再⒕夏募骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰握吐乓咴线萌琶刷俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰摺独杳阁筠滏津如猕并兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景集骈屐渚集箬徜秣尖祜汶豉疱舰灬篝咪殓轸殇舰ㄑ煺套ょ壬ノ肆细、炯忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南阿尖祜汶豉疱舰泔铘蝻祗哝祜鬟篝狒屙孱趔殇舰郝戢Ａō哉鳊馇愎窖⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰铺献⒕乱帕思骈屐渚集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟荐犰蹂钺礤舰优孟文英尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰侪破瓒制箢煳妒温位⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰泔铘蝻祗唑屦遽暨屮簪殇舰嗣ㄊ癯貅汹趔竦鱿刀娶泔祆狃箦浣Ⅳ蝓澧荐犰蹂钺礤舰陨团英尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳咩镱篝犷簪殇舰瞠馐污牡煦泊鹣彤匍⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰孟斡粤卧⒕晌粕紊再集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰糸礤秕簪殇舰飓惶甭匣癞彐销ｊ董噜⒕俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰陨团险杂粤盟⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮箦簪殇舰逊种帜帜砌贝憷阝珊⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰邮腐遁瘁茂科猿鳎尧句殓轸奔骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞尖祜汶豉疱舰扉篝筮珏羯钿屮殇舰鳆为抻窒躏筛Ｏ庾响⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱篝狒屙孱艚㈡犰箦狒舰趄蹂⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰拖呐⒕桥约骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰兹乓泞酒蚁瓦盼募骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞尖祜汶豉疱舰灬篝拈玳籼轶簪殇舰后稠舯斌规墟彗浦徵碲⒕集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰猎⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰翕夭烁彪椹匆鄢嬗尧兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷颈集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮箦簪殇舰核’羰钎河拉谒⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰裱刺唤扰啕霏ろ伸殁⒕溟玳布骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞尖祜汶豉疱舰扉篝筮珏羯钿屮殇舰苑摔蹈―猸嵇吒凇逅⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱篝狒屙孱艚㈡犰箦狒舰趄蹂⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰拖呐⒕桥约骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰兹乓泞酒蚁瓦盼募骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞尖祜汶豉疱舰灬篝拈玳籼轶簪殇舰花险漭咆钳对撵蝈涌蝣⒕集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰猎⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰缏塌硼相秣错魉恻啖兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷静集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰翦暨觑轭殇舰舀穑羽瞵踩辰挪螽褥症兼殄熹钺礤舰至疑谅膛殇舰的揄毫锟蛩迟哞慑英眷狍溟玳豇艏骈屐渚俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰釉撩刷尖祜汶豉疱舰翦暨篝狒屙孱簪殇舰腭豳荸裹洗绵敷模额⒕荐犰蹂钺礤舰耘卦⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰霏桫蹭尤觜哐鹧匣垦菲⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕灬篝溟玳趔集骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰翦暨篝狒屙孱簪殇舰肺馍亵仨廨缢劢驿啷⒕荐犰蹂钺礤舰耘卦⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰秕穑墒饮甙沈镄辔铄⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕集骈屐渚集箬徜秣尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰掺世菪湎绛跤ぴ秸⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰邮腐遁瘁茂科猿鳎尧句殓轸奔骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰翦暨篝狒屙孱簪殇舰唛┝沌达续毗ā卑珐孝荐犰蹂钺礤舰耘卦⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰谮茹娆悴鼠ㄛ羁姥铢佗兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕集骈屐渚集箬徜秣尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰┭艉ㄞ孙嶷谈觯鞫刻崃⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰裱刺唤扰啕霏ろ伸殁⒕溟玳布骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰铒糸纟殇舰黼Ｚ锔妈卣召垢娶兼殄熹钺礤舰蜗陨粕昧陨衔咴傩泞倔蹉沐篌集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰蜗陨粕昧陨衔哂险文⒕箝戾铘集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰团佑燎泞俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰捏印感鲩豹佻航鸢佗兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕徕慵骈屐渚集箬徜秣尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰禁霸∏骒籼奕跋ㄌ鲞⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰的揄毫锟蛩迟哞慑英眷狍溟玳豇艏骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰泔铘蝻祗唛姊殇舰燎雌螵皓〗翳淹疤蔻荐犰蹂钺礤舰善阿尖祜汶豉疱舰祜玳氵镳弪狒轱睥殇舰洛妤掼瘕蠕跋瘸猩英兼殄熹钺礤舰闲⒕廖募骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰立尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮蜻痱镳弪豉殇舰稚孜骒吝于ヨ篮蜷螨⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱溟鲩箫蜻轭瘐艚㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰幸闲乓再⒕胖盼集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰握吐乓咴线萌琶刷俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰慊椴桡瞿缴寡跣恒丌兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景集骈屐渚集箬徜秣尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰箩鲳媛袷旦骣榉锖耽兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰邮腐遁瘁茂科猿鳎尧句殓轸奔骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰垄尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮蜻痱镳弪豉殇舰呈钻垧恼揶襁吕挈兑廷柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱溟鲩箫蜻轭瘐艚㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰幸闲乓再⒕胖盼集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰握吐乓咴线萌琶刷俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰慊椴桡瞿缴寡跣恒丌兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景集骈屐渚集箬徜秣尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰颂⊙酵塌堕付え阿兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰裱刺唤扰啕霏ろ伸殁⒕溟玳布骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南阿尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮箦簪殇舰邸ｇ鲩跏孽Ａび镱笆盐⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰娓泣由凯柯霜磐职羝竣惧铘蝙痫轭艏骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰螭娑显练掷嗔邶ū挞兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷颈集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰泔铘蝻祗哝祜鬟篝狒屙孱趔殇舰ァ酶凑旌坐懂纺∵瘼兼殄熹钺礤舰铺献⒕乱帕思骈屐渚集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟荐犰蹂钺礤舰优孟文英尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰瓜蕾禳观残浴桊腭蒋发兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰趄徜暹溴骈铋糸镱唪蜥溴镳糸镱螈殇舰册姨仡∏促抵蝰聿姿瓮⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱栳筮骈蝮暨忉蝌殄蚪㈡犰箦栳筮箦泔钿哜狎蜷弪舰驷祗澧栳筮痱邃殂糸镱舰驷祗澧炯眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰恼伊陨衔再信咛捎寓爵集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰恼伊陨衔⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰庶券痫秤棵捞冯什鎏蘑兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷颈集骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰镣险卧⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰奕淀笨礤ｒ谁勾ミ腼蔻兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷颈集骈屐渚集箬徜秣尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰莸澳揍仄忤想晖餍舯傺⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰揭诓的鲍揿奄觏而⒕晌稍闪釉了偶骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖尖祜汶豉疱舰徭翦蜻瘐蜚栳箦殇舰巷绮跆こ藿碓边舐潍泔祆狃箦浣Ⅳ蝓澧舰烦雹舰北阿俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰疗耘倚找萌劣胚釉撩刷尖祜汶豉疱舰泔铘蝻祗唛姊殇舰鼠丁此∶い任稍亿将并柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱屐箦殒舰雹屐箦舰雹炯眭翎糸镱荐犰蹂钺礤舰善阿尖祜汶豉疱舰祜玳氵泔眇狎澧殇舰凰锆缧滔笼折璜ぃ凡⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰闲⒕窃偶骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰立尖祜汶豉疱舰麸翎爝痱镦轸殇舰甯毯月猫恼傍绘仉▲⒕集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰垄尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰四梨趁规狮标挛吭⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰文晷ó毕Ｑ稽议榜砩⒕粤伺幸掀稍集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南阿尖祜汶豉疱舰翦暨痱轭簪殇舰搬瘳婶毛宋銮榈鲡搠⒕荐犰蹂钺礤舰耘卦⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰饮峪嘹淑诉谧肀板芒兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕栝犷蝓睢集骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟荐犰蹂钺礤舰善雹尖祜汶豉疱舰祜玳氵泔眇狎澧殇舰库丽弗谠苞林蓐轼蕻挞兼殄熹钺礤舰闲⒕淘偶骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰立尖祜汶豉疱舰麸翎爝痱镦轸殇舰嫔耨檄固珙赚├寸∥褐⒕集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰垄尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳唧轭珈澧殇舰诵癞赂日乓冻佼腰洽兼殄熹钺礤舰闲⒕闻羌骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰握廷俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰氦濯ｄ锅封篼彪缀幕⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷竟集骈屐渚集箬徜秣尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰债猴炝觯┆╇趼坌改该⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰婷蛭赧烁冬痼痖亿瓶娶居韵滔佑集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南雹尖祜汶豉疱舰翦暨痱轭簪殇舰缜祜琬鸫槌淘鲠概巳铫荐犰蹂钺礤舰耘卦⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰古锻礻潇版侈汜翎玛英兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕趄徵衢铄糸礤集骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰盘优⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰泔铘蝻祗唛姊殇舰啾嫒汇ㄝ悴兕灰匀坭驿⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱屐箦舰雹炯眭翎糸镱荐犰蹂钺礤舰善阿尖祜汶豉疱舰泔铘蜥泗咩桢汶唑弩蹯簪殇舰束棼╃∧捎羔衢Ｚ孩兼殄熹钺礤舰萌琶诉遗诱淘⒕鏖罴骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南阿尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮箦簪殇舰鄞痢辈啾╄郯澉衩琚兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰揭诓的鲍揿奄觏而⒕晌稍闪釉了偶骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰莓崔溃棼窝跷簇啮勘⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰崮吧残兴仇啐晾鲡靶⒕釉了偶骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰盘优⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮箦簪殇舰撼钌帘腭邗溺叨馄敉⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰揭诓的鲍揿奄觏而⒕晌稍闪釉了偶骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哚蜷翳礤糸恽殇舰奢茫漫衬撒亻镌谠诣微兼殄熹钺礤舰闲⒕驼淘尚藤集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰立俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰浞蜱と颢万藐伲叁阿兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷颈集骈屐渚集箬徜秣尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰愦丹灏殖父戢伦县岢⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰揭诓的鲍揿奄觏而⒕晌稍闪釉了偶骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰垄俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰桧嫠绶乒攘ほ责讲⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷颈集骈屐渚集箬徜秣尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰笫孤瀚葚掰弭攘悻瘪⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰乒乳猸茫翱少沧滇喋纰就烈陨橇膛集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰趄徜暹徵衢睥殇舰婷阎陡毁舂┫糈僦筱⒕集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖尖祜汶豉疱舰忮骘蝈唣躜汨狍澧殇舰毡靶川抑沉觇骂屺傣缀泔祆狃箦浣Ⅳ蝓澧溴戾翎忪褰㈡犰箦舰阿舰卑洞⒕俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰屡葡遗姓颐攘优哂粤盟⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰泔铘蝻祗唛姊殇舰幺硭睁盖兔顺光房哧⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱屐箦舰雹炯眭翎糸镱荐犰蹂钺礤舰善阿尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮蜻痱镳弪豉殇舰嫡檠萤梁炭帻抨螯脾柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱溟鲩箫蜻轭瘐艚㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰幸闲乓再⒕胖盼集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰握吐乓咴线萌琶刷俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰摺独杳阁筠滏津如猕并兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景集骈屐渚集箬徜秣尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰┄拄撞噘幌髋厣嗲へ骟⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰娓泣由凯柯霜磐职羝竣惧铘蝙痫轭艏骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南阿尖祜汶豉疱舰瘐蜚栳箦殇舰麦辛蝽昶藓洲醣昱笆冖兼殄熹钺礤舰姓颐攘优咛捎寓灸汕稍夏募骈屐渚集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰盘优⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰瘐蜚栳箦殇舰晗输醵胧赦《氏蠢菇⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰姓颐攘优咛捎寓灸汕稍夏募骈屐渚集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖集盱